Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[Reborn from the Ashes]
[ولدت من الرماد]
[Episode 8]
[الحلقة 8]
This is our bridal chamber.
هذه هي غرفة زفافنا.
You dared to kill me.
لقد تجرأت على قتلي.
That was an accident. I never meant to.
لقد كان ذلك حادثًا. لم أقصد ذلك أبدًا.
Woman,
امرأة،
you're not being honest.
أنت لست صادقا.
I clearly pushed him off the cliff. Why is he unharmed?
لقد دفعته بوضوح من فوق الجرف. لماذا لم يُصَب بأذى؟
I...
أنا...
I was just too scared.
لقد كنت خائفة جداً.
At the cliff,
عند الجرف،
I saw the silver spear on your chest.
لقد رأيت الرمح الفضي على صدرك.
Startled, I pushed you.
لقد فزعت ودفعتك.
I didn't expect you to actually fall.
لم أتوقع أنك سوف تسقط فعليا.
Didn't you say you couldn't see it before?
ألم تقل أنك لم تتمكن من رؤيته من قبل؟
That day at the Begonia House,
في ذلك اليوم في بيت بيجونيا،
I saw it clearly.
لقد رأيته بوضوح.
That scene terrified me,
لقد أرعبني هذا المشهد،
so I stayed silent and hid the truth.
لذلك التزمت الصمت وأخفيت الحقيقة.
Since you can see it,
بما أنك تستطيع رؤيته،
then help me pull it out.
ثم ساعدني على سحبه.
I'm not lying to you.
أنا لا أكذب عليك.
I really can see it.
أنا حقا أستطيع أن أرى ذلك.
But I can't reach it.
ولكن لا أستطيع الوصول إليه.
It's right here.
إنه هنا.
Only she can see this spear.
هي وحدها من تستطيع رؤية هذا الرمح.
Maybe one day
ربما يوما ما
she will be able to help me pull it out.
سوف تكون قادرة على مساعدتي في إخراجه.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
This poison
هذا السم
flairs up once every month.
يشتعل مرة كل شهر.
If you behave well,
إذا تصرفت بشكل جيد،
I'll give you the antidote on time.
سأعطيك الترياق في الوقت المناسب.
But if you speak out of turn,
ولكن إذا تحدثت خارج دورك،
or do what you shouldn't,
أو افعل ما لا ينبغي لك فعله،
then
ثم
hell will welcome you.
الجحيم سوف يرحب بك.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
Well?
حسنًا؟
Just as you expected,
كما توقعت تماما،
after you ran away from the wedding,
بعد أن هربت من حفل الزفاف،
the Prince was extremely angry.
وكان الأمير غاضبا للغاية.
Wanyan Jin actually took the initiative to marry Su Qingran.
في الواقع، اتخذ وان يان جين زمام المبادرة للزواج من سو تشينغران.
I intentionally reported until after their wedding night.
لقد قمت عمدا بالإبلاغ عن ذلك حتى بعد ليلة زفافهما.
You're saying Wanyan Jin
أنت تقول وانيان جين
took initiative to propose to marry Su Qingran.
أخذت زمام المبادرة لطلب الزواج من سو تشينغران.
Yes.
نعم.
That caught me by surprise.
لقد فاجأني ذلك.
However,
لكن،
since their fate is sealed,
لأن مصيرهم محسوم،
let's return now.
دعونا نعود الآن.
I want Father to help me
أريد من الأب أن يساعدني
to formally propose to the Su Family again.
لتقديم طلب الزواج رسميًا لعائلة سو مرة أخرى.
This time, no one will stop me from marrying Yi.
هذه المرة، لن يمنعني أحد من الزواج من يي.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
on the wedding day,
في يوم الزفاف،
[Prince Zhenbei's Mansion Hall] the bride actually ran off with a man.
[قاعة قصر الأمير تشنباي] العروس هربت بالفعل مع رجل.
Isn't this a slap in the face to us?
أليس هذا صفعة في وجهنا؟
And Jin.
وجين.
He even brought such a woman
حتى أنه أحضر مثل هذه المرأة
back to the Mansion
العودة إلى القصر
and secretly held a ceremonial wedding with her.
وأقام معها حفل زفاف سريًا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
You don't need to say anything more about this.
لا تحتاج إلى قول المزيد عن هذا.
Jin has already told me everything that happened.
لقد أخبرني جين بالفعل بكل ما حدث.
Isn't what he did a disgrace to the Mansion?
أليس ما فعله عارًا للقصر؟
In my opinion,
في رأيي،
he never truly cared about the Mansion.
لم يكن يهتم حقًا بالقصر أبدًا.
He actually did the right thing.
لقد فعل الشيء الصحيح فعلا.
He did this for the greater good,
لقد فعل هذا من أجل الصالح العام،
though it was a grievance for him
على الرغم من أنها كانت مظلمة بالنسبة له
to enter into such a marriage.
للدخول في مثل هذا الزواج.
Your Highness, this concerns the reputation of the Mansion.
صاحب السمو، هذا الأمر يتعلق بسمعة القصر.
How can you be so biased towards him?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون متحيزًا تجاهه إلى هذا الحد؟
Could it be that
هل يمكن أن يكون ذلك
you want me to protect
تريد مني أن أحميك
that rebellious son who fled at the last minute?
ذلك الابن المتمرد الذي هرب في اللحظة الأخيرة؟
If you have time for that,
إذا كان لديك الوقت لذلك،
you'd better think carefully
من الأفضل أن تفكر بعناية
about how to discipline your son.
حول كيفية تأديب ابنك.
No matter what,
مهما كان الأمر،
I refuse to accept this marriage.
أرفض قبول هذا الزواج.
Last night, we finished the ceremony
انتهينا من الحفل الليلة الماضية
and consummated our marriage.
وأتممنا زواجنا.
Mother, you have to accept it.
أمي، عليك أن تقبلي ذلك.
Pay my respects to you, Father, Mother.
أتقدم باحتراماتي لكم يا أبي، يا أمي.
Why are you wearing a veil?
لماذا ترتدين الحجاب؟
Do you still have us in your eyes?
هل لا زالنا في عينيك؟
Yesterday, she was abducted by someone.
لقد تم اختطافها بالأمس من قبل شخص ما.
It's not proper for her to be seen right now.
ليس من المناسب رؤيتها الآن.
She is also afraid of offending you.
وهي أيضًا خائفة من إهانتك.
That's why she wears the veil.
ولهذا السبب ترتدي الحجاب.
So I was just overthinking.
لذلك كنت أفكر كثيرًا.
Su Qingran, from now on, you will be the crown princess.
سو تشينغران، من الآن فصاعدا، سوف تكونين أميرة التاج.
Take good care of Jin,
اعتني جيدا بجين
and always remember your status.
وتذكر دائمًا حالتك.
Enough.
كافٍ.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
we are one family.
نحن عائلة واحدة.
Just stop preaching here.
فقط توقف عن الوعظ هنا.
The bride will offer tea.
العروسة ستقدم الشاي.
Father.
أب.
For such a corrupt official,
بالنسبة لمثل هذا المسؤول الفاسد،
I will personally supervise the execution.
سأشرف شخصيا على التنفيذ.
It's a proven fact
إنها حقيقة مثبتة
that the criminal Wen Muchen poisoned the Qilin Army.
أن المجرم وين موتشين هو من سمم جيش تشيلين.
His crimes are unforgivable.
جرائمه لا تغتفر.
Carry out the execution.
تنفيذ الإعدام.
You vile woman!
يا لك من امرأة حقيرة!
Reflect carefully here.
فكر جيدا هنا.
[Memorial Tablet of Wen Muchen]
[لوحة تذكارية لوين موتشين]
Why are you...
لماذا انت...؟
Mother, who do you think I am?
أمي من تظنين أنني؟
Mind your behavior.
انتبه لسلوكك.
Your Highness, forgive me. I was mistaken.
سموكم، سامحني. لقد كنت مخطئا.
Since the tea is too hot, why not let it cool down?
بما أن الشاي ساخن جدًا، فلماذا لا نتركه يبرد؟
That brat,
هذا الطفل المدلل
after gaining recognition, he no longer takes me seriously.
بعد أن حصل على الاعتراف، لم يعد يأخذني على محمل الجد.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
Young Master Qi has returned.
لقد عاد السيد الشاب تشي.
He dares to come back again?
هل يجرؤ على العودة مرة أخرى؟
Father, Mother.
الأب، الأم.
I know I have caused trouble.
أعلم أنني تسببت في مشكلة.
I ask you to punish me.
أطلب منك أن تعاقبني.
Qi, what you did was indeed wrong this time.
تشي، ما فعلته كان خطأً بالفعل هذه المرة.
But Jin and Ran look well-matched.
لكن جين وران يبدو أنهما متوافقان بشكل جيد.
It was a twist of fate that brought about a good marriage.
لقد كانت مفاجأة القدر التي أدت إلى زواج سعيد.
Though your merits outweigh your mistakes,
على الرغم من أن مزاياك تفوق أخطائك،
you must still accept punishment.
لا يزال يتعين عليك قبول العقوبة.
Qi, hurry and apologize to your sister-in-law.
تشي، سارع بالاعتذار لأخت زوجتك.
Bad bamboo never grows good shoots.
الخيزران السيئ لا ينتج براعم جيدة أبدًا.
Wanyan Qi has caused such a big mess.
لقد تسبب وانيان تشي في فوضى كبيرة.
She thinks a simple apology will put everything to rest.
إنها تعتقد أن اعتذارًا بسيطًا سيضع كل شيء في نصابه الصحيح.
I refuse to let things go that easily.
أرفض أن أترك الأمور تسير بهذه السهولة.
I am willing to apologize to you.
أنا على استعداد للاعتذار لك.
How do you intend to apologize?
كيف تنوي الإعتذار؟
Your way of making an apology is quite unique.
طريقتك في الاعتذار فريدة من نوعها.
Qi,
تشي،
how could you be so disrespectful to Qingran?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون غير محترم تجاه تشينغران؟
Qi must also think
يجب على تشي أن يفكر أيضًا
that it was improper for the bride to serve tea
أنه من غير اللائق أن تقدم العروس الشاي
while wearing a veil
بينما ترتدي الحجاب
and not showing her true face.
وعدم إظهار وجهها الحقيقي.
There's no outsider present now,
لا يوجد أي شخص خارجي حاضر الآن،
so why not just lift the veil?
فلماذا لا نرفع الحجاب فحسب؟
Yes, Mother.
نعم أمي.
That was exactly my thought just now.
لقد كانت هذه بالضبط فكرتي الآن.
Since Qingran
منذ تشينغران
has married into the family, she is now one of us,
لقد تزوجت من أحد أفراد العائلة، وهي الآن واحدة منا،
and appearing with a veil
ويظهر بحجاب
seems a bit distant.
يبدو بعيدًا بعض الشيء.
If you're so eager to see my face,
إذا كنت متشوقًا جدًا لرؤية وجهي،
then I'll show it to you.
ثم سأعرضه عليك.
But,
لكن،
please don't be afraid.
من فضلك لا تخف.
You...
أنت...
This is impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
How could you possibly still be alive?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون لا تزال على قيد الحياة؟
Why does she look so much like Wen Yueqian?
لماذا تشبه إلى حد كبير وين يوي تشيان؟
Indeed.
بالفعل.
I was never supposed to survive.
لم يكن من المفترض أن أبقى على قيد الحياة أبدًا.
Are you here to demand my life?
هل أنت هنا للمطالبة بحياتي؟
On my wedding day, I was abducted.
في يوم زفافي، تم اختطافي.
If it weren't for his arrival,
لو لم يكن لوصوله،
I might not have survived.
ربما لم أكن على قيد الحياة.
Qi, no need to be so tense.
تشي، لا داعي لأن تكون متوتراً جداً.
Even if you ran off and brought me shame,
حتى لو هربت وجلبت لي العار،
I wouldn't come here to demand your life.
لن آتي إلى هنا للمطالبة بحياتك.
My wife only has a small cut on her face.
زوجتي لديها قطع صغير فقط في وجهها.
Is it really necessary for you to react this strongly?
هل من الضروري حقا أن تتفاعل بهذه القوة؟
Impossible!
مستحيل!
How could there be someone so alike?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك شخص مماثل؟
Father,
أب،
she must be that vile woman.
لا بد أن تكون تلك المرأة الحقيرة.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
I don't understand why Qi says this about me,
لا أفهم لماذا يقول تشي هذا عني،
even going so far as to insult me.
حتى أنهم وصلوا إلى حد إهانتي.
This woman knows how to stir trouble.
هذه المرأة تعرف كيف تثير المشاكل.
Qi,
تشي،
she is already my wife.
إنها زوجتي بالفعل.
How can you insult her like this?
كيف يمكنك إهانتها بهذه الطريقة؟
Father,
أب،
you must stand up for Qingran.
يجب عليك الدفاع عن تشينغران.
You rebellious son!
يا ابني المتمرد!
You reneged on the marriage you begged for.
لقد تراجعت عن الزواج الذي توسلت إليه.
If Jin hadn't stepped in on time,
لو لم يتدخل جين في الوقت المناسب،
you've completely made me lose face.
لقد جعلتني أفقد وجهي تماما.
Now you're still humiliating Qingran.
الآن أنت لا تزال تهين تشينغران.
Someone!
شخص ما!
Take him away.
خذه بعيدا.
Flog him 20 times.
اجلدوه عشرين مرة.
Father, I was wrong.
أبي لقد كنت مخطئا.
Go kneel in the ancestral hall for three days.
اذهب واركع في القاعة الأجدادية لمدة ثلاثة أيام.
Reflect carefully.
فكر جيدا.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
You can't do that.
لا يمكنك فعل ذلك.
Qi is quite frail.
تشي ضعيف جدًا.
20 lashes,
20 جلدة
he won't be able to endure that.
لن يكون قادرا على تحمل ذلك.
I've heard,
لقد سمعت
that Prince Zhenbei's Mansion has very strict family rules.
أن قصر الأمير تشنباي لديه قواعد عائلية صارمة للغاية.
It truly lives up to the reputation.
إنه يرقى حقا إلى مستوى السمعة.
Qi has become like this now,
لقد أصبح تشي مثل هذا الآن،
all because you spoiled him.
كل هذا لأنك أفسدته.
If you dare to plead again,
إذا تجرأت على التوسل مرة أخرى،
I'll add 20 more lashes.
سأضيف 20 رمشًا إضافيًا.
It's all because of this jinx.
كل هذا بسبب هذا النحس.
Ever since she married into the Mansion, the household has been in turmoil.
منذ أن تزوجت من القصر، كان المنزل في حالة من الاضطراب.
Father, Mother,
الأب، الأم،
if there's nothing else,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر،
we will take our leave first.
سوف نأخذ إجازتنا أولاً.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Everything
كل شئ
has just begun.
لقد بدأت للتو.
[The Crown Prince's Courtyard]
[فناء ولي العهد]
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
You really hold grudges.
أنت حقا تحمل ضغائن.
You poisoned me last night,
لقد سممتني الليلة الماضية،
and punish me to dig lotus roots for you today.
وعاقبني بأن أحفر لك جذور اللوتس اليوم.
You're overthinking.
أنت تفكر كثيرًا.
I just want to eat the lotus roots you dug yourself.
أريد فقط أن آكل جذور اللوتس التي حفرتها بنفسك.
You've offended Princess Zhenbei and Wanyan Qi.
لقد أسأت إلى الأميرة تشنباي ووان يان تشي.
Aren't you worried they'll come after you?
ألا تشعر بالقلق من أنهم سيأتون خلفك؟
Aren't you the one who offended them?
أليس أنت من أساء إليهم؟
You really cleared the way cleanly.
لقد قمت بالفعل بتطهير الطريق بشكل نظيف.
Aren't you enjoying it just as much?
ألا تستمتع بذلك تمامًا؟
They seem quite fearful of your looks.
يبدو أنهم خائفون جدًا من مظهرك.
The world is vast.
العالم واسع .
It's no surprise two people can look alike.
ليس من المستغرب أن يكون شخصان متشابهين.
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
then I won't be helping you anymore.
إذن لن أساعدك بعد الآن.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
don't be so absolute with your words.
لا تكن مطلقًا في كلماتك.
Or else,
أو غير ذلك،
you will lose face.
سوف تفقد وجهك.
Don't forget,
لا تنسى،
your life
حياتك
is in my hands.
هو في يدي.
If I die,
إذا مت
no one would help you pull the spear for you.
لن يساعدك أحد في سحب الرمح نيابة عنك.
My Lord,
سيدي
we've found it.
لقد وجدناه.
The woman Wanyan Qi married before
المرأة التي تزوجها وانيان تشي من قبل
was Wen Yueqian, the only daughter of former Governor Wen Muchen.
كانت وين يويتشيان، الابنة الوحيدة للحاكم السابق وين موتشين.
After Wen Muchen was executed,
بعد إعدام وين موتشين،
Wen Yueqian mysteriously fell ill and died.
أصيب ون يوي تشيان بمرض غامض ومات.
Wen Yueqian...
وين يويه تشيان...
Qianyue.
تشيانيو.
Yueqian.
يويهتشيان.
♪In this world, who exactly♪
???في هذا العالم من بالضبط؟؟؟
♪Pushed me into the abyss?♪
???دفعني إلى الهاوية ؟؟؟؟
♪The sky is silent, and the sea says nothing♪
"السماء صامتة والبحر لا يقول شيئا"
♪Who shows me mercy in this world?♪
???من يرحمني في الدنيا؟؟؟؟
♪Cold winds sweep across the wasteland♪
???رياح باردة تكتسح الأرض القاحلة؟؟؟
♪Mercilessly gifting me snow and frost♪
???يمنحني الثلج والصقيع بلا رحمة؟؟؟
♪In this fleeting life♪
''في هذه الحياة العابرة''
♪No mercy, no answers♪
???لا رحمة، لا إجابات؟؟؟
♪Yet one lamp shines, unafraid to go out♪
ومع ذلك فإن مصباحًا واحدًا يضيء، ولا يخاف من الانطفاء؟؟؟
♪Time can twist, but people aren't perfect♪
???قد يتغير الزمن، لكن الناس ليسوا كاملين؟؟؟
♪Who decides who comes and who parts?♪
???من يقرر من يأتي ومن يفارق ؟؟؟؟
♪It all rests on a single hopeful thought♪
"كل هذا يعتمد على فكرة واحدة مفعمة بالأمل"
♪Why fear one last breath?♪
لماذا الخوف من النفس الأخير؟
♪Love is brief, full of regrets♪
???الحب قصير، مليء بالندم؟؟؟
♪I paint the sky as a fan♪
???أرسم السماء كمروحة؟؟؟
♪To blow away nightmares and scatter the dust♪
???لإزالة الكوابيس وتبديد الغبار؟؟؟
♪Can't resist the fate of being separated♪
???لا تستطيع مقاومة مصير الانفصال؟؟؟
♪By distance♪
???بالمسافة؟؟؟
[Exclusive content rights reserved]
[حقوق المحتوى الحصري محفوظة]
[by Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[من قبل شركة يوكو لتكنولوجيا المعلومات (بكين) المحدودة]